hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
Look, Papa!
What is it, Kunihisa?
Look, it's sparkly and pretty.
That's right, Kunihisa.
Even though it's so pretty,
how can it have no value?
That's horrible, isn't it, Papa?
Impossible!
Celeb Ninja
Technique
- Kinton Jutsu
Are you serious, Grandma Tsunade!
Calm down!
Sorry, I'll calm down.
Since he is an important person,
I believe there is no one better
for the job other than you.
Finally... Finally a mission
appropriate for my abilities.
Guarding an important person...
It has such a nice ring to it!
Listen closely!
Gotcha.
Okay, about this mission...
— Shizune.
— Yes!
The details are written in
those documents.
His name's Kunihisa,
he lives in the capital.
He's the heir of
an old acquaintance of mine.
Your acquaintance, Grandma Tsunade?
Yes, his father's name is Kunijiro.
He made his fortune in one generation.
He's a successful jeweler.
The heir of a jeweler...
Hey, Papa?
Is this real, too?
Of course it's real, little Kuni.
So, is that and that and this
and the one over there too?!
Of course, little Kuni!
Ninja! Ninja! Ninja!
Suddenly my motivation is boosted!
I'll do it! I'll do that mission!
So where is this Kunihisa at,
Grandma Tsunade?!
Come in!
— Ninja! Ninja! Ninja!
— Wow! Who's this brat?
Ninja! Ninja! Ninja! Ninja!
Ninja?
Don't add that question
at the end of your sentence!
So it must be you!
You are the kid who's going with Kunihisa
to play a Ninja for a day...
I'll leave him to you, then.
What? Be a Ninja for a day...?
My little Kuni really admires Ninja,
and he aggravates me by saying
nothing but Ninja every day.
Grandma Tsunade!
Wasn't this
a guarding an important person mission?!
What are you talking about?
I did say he's an important person,
but didn't say a word about
guarding him.
I was fooled! Grandma!
Uzumaki Naruto!
I order you to play be
a Ninja for a day with Kunihisa!
Damn... That's a dirty trick, Grandma!
Oh, there's one more thing.
I added your regular missions
as a service.
Oh, that's cruel, Grandma Tsunade!
Clean the pond, repair the bridge,
get rid of the savage pig,
and...
It turns out that babysitting is just
added to the regular D-rank missions!
Ninja, Ninja.
Watch this, Kunihisa!
I'll teach you the awesomeness
of a Ninja.
Hey, awesome Naruto! Awesome!
It's Be a Ninja for a Day day, isn't it?
So Kunihisa, you gather garbage
from over there, too.
Okay!
Oh, that's right.
Don't go into the marsh.
This marsh is bottomless,
so once you're caught,
you can't get out.
Huh, what?
— Oh, no, Young Master is in trouble!
— Naruto!
What are you doing?!
You fool! I'll save you,
so you stay right there!
Fool! I'll be fine.
You'll be fine?
I can handle this kind of simple task
with my Ninjutsu.
Ninjutsu?
— Oh, no! Young Master!
— Oh, no!
Alligator, Snapping Turtle, Piranha, Toad!
Money Style:
Help Me Jutsu!
What?!
Mine!
Wha...?! Wha...?!
I'm fine!
What are you guys doing?!
If you want money,
hurry up and rescue me.
What good would increasing
the victims do?
Hey, Kunihisa.
Who are they?
Oh, them...
Papa employs them and
they protect me if I get into trouble.
Really.
That's right, for example...
There!
See!
What do you mean "see"?!
Is it okay?
I said it's okay!
Really, really okay?
What are you so freaked out about?
It's okay!
But still, it's scary!
Cut the bull and come here now!
Right!
But just before that...
Ninja Art: Scapegoat Jutsu!
See? It's fine.
Come here, quick!
If I get on it next,
I think it might break...
Let's check out a bunch more.
I'm not finished yet! More of you!
Go!
What the...?!
Just as I thought.
I thought I was gonna die.
What were you doing, Kunihisa?!
What would have happened
if I'd got on the bridge like that?
Come on you!
Okay, everyone, your compensation!
Here!
I'm telling you, stop that!
That kid...
He's got money, huh, Big Brother.
Yeah... And his main guard
is a single Genin.
Big Brother, it's decided.
Yeah.
What's next?
Get rid of the savage pig
who appears in the field ahead.
Okay! I'll do my best!
What the...?!
A savage pig...?
More like a monster!
Crap!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
That's cool!
Naruto!
Okay! It's my turn this time!
Fool! What are you doing?
Hurry up and escape!
Here I go!
Ninja Art: Money Clone Jutsu!
Money Clone?!
Hey, you ugly savage pig!
Starting now,
I, Kunihisa, will punish you!
Go!
Go! Get him! There!
What, nobody wants to eat your meat!
You dummy!
He ordered all of this!
What?!
I didn't want to,
but he forced me to...
Wait...
That's a lie. It's a misunderstanding!
Those are false charges!
Forgive me! Naruto...
I... How should I put this...?
really hate guys like you!
Why are you getting so testy?
Jeez, poor people just can't help
that they have short tempers...
This'll put you back in a good mood.
Take as much as you want!
Enough already!
I'm telling you to stop
doing stuff like that!
Why?
It's a big mistake to think that
anything can be resolved with money!
There are times when you have
to use your own power!
There hasn't been anything that
I couldn't do with money so far!
You... Are you always like this?
With that personality,
you can't make friends!
It's okay 'cause
I can buy friends with money!
What...?
You... Buy friends? You mean...
If I give 'em money,
everybody will be my friend!
Kunihisa...
That's why I hate country Ninja.
They're cheap and stink of poverty...
Stupid!
Oh, please wait, Master Kunihisa!
Running made me hungry.
Take this and buy a boxed lunch!
There's nothing like a store
to buy lunch around here.
Well, snacks will be fine!
There's no convenience store
or candy shop...
You're useless!
This is why I hate the country!
Stupid Naruto.
What's that?
Oh, Young Master!
Little fish, little fish!
Let's eat!
The kid must be stupid to get
caught in this cheap trick.
— Don't you agree, Bro?
— Yeah!
Naruto?!
Aw man,
you're really high maintenance.
Those two guys just now...
They were going to catch you!
They were plotting a kidnapping,
whatever...
Whatever...?
I'm often a target,
because I have money.
Often a target...? You...
More importantly,
I want to eat more fish!
Go find a shop and buy some.
You... Still think you can do
anything with money?
All right, watch this!
Awesome! Awesome Naruto!
How's that?!
You can just get things using
your own power without using money.
Even... without using money?
Damn!
He attacked us by surprise,
that cowardly bastard.
I'll give it back to him double!
Well, wait...
If we do it thoughtlessly,
we'll just get creamed again.
So, what do we do?
We'll use that thing.
That thing...?
Look close at the movement
of the fish...
Aim for the instant when
they fall after jumping up.
Don't get hasty.
Now!
That was close!
One more time, Naruto!
I'll get the Kunai knife,
so one more time!
Master Kunihisa!
— It's deep over there!
— Please be careful!
I know, I know...
Where did it go?
I think it's in this area, but...
I won't let you get away this time!
You guys...
We hired these guys with
the money you threw away.
It means that now,
they're on our side...
Hey, you guys! I'll pay you double
what those guys did!
So be on my side...
What the...?
Looks like you've run out of money.
How about you guys over there?
Wanna join us?
We'll pay up stacks of money.
These guys have been
with me for a long time.
That paltry sum won't...
We're not going along with
your selfish acts any longer!
You guys?!
No! I don't like it!
Annoying brat. I'll have to tie you up
so you won't move.
What are you doing, Kunihisa?!
Naruto, I... I...
It's fine already!
Hey, you... I'll pay you double
what you get for your mission.
Won't you hand that brat over to us?
We're just going to demand
ransom money from his parents is all.
We won't kill him.
Relax and hand him over.
It's not enough?
Here, how about this?
Naruto...
Kunihisa! Ride on my back!
Okay.
Still not enough, huh? Here!
That's all of it! Take it!
Like I said...
It's a big mistake to think
you can obtain anything with money!
Crap!
After them!
Listen! Hold on tightly Kunihisa.
Okay!
Damn! I can't move
with him on my back!
I can't see the bottom, Naruto...
Go!
Okay! You go on ahead.
What?! Go on ahead?!
There he is! Let's get him!
— Yeah!
What are you doing?!
It's okay! Hurry up and jump!
I can't... I'm scared, Naruto!
It's not scary, come on!
I can't... I'm scared...!
Damn it!
Do it!
Naruto!
Well, you're coming with me!
Hurry! Kunihisa!
But...
It's okay... You can definitely do this!
Prepare yourself!
No way!
Go, Kunihisa!
Oh, Big Brother!
Kunihisa?!
It hurts!
I'm going to clean those guys out
and then I'll be right over!
So wait a second!
Daruto...
Darudo!
The wall's collapsing... Escape!
How long are you guys gonna be
on top of me!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
What's going on?!
I have to go to him!
There are times when you have
to use your own power!
Use my own... power!
You can just get things using
your own power without using money.
Even without money...
with my own power!
I can... do this!
Just one step short!
Naruto!
Kunihisa!
No! A little bit more!
— We did it!
All right!
It hurts but...
I'm scared but...
I...
You... What a face?!
Kunihisa...
You did a good job!
Darudo!
Wha...?!
Hold on, don't drip snot!
But Naruto!
Stop it!
Well... See ya!
Yeah! Next time you come play
at my house, Naruto!
Okay!
Really... You took great care of him.
Thank you!
Yeah, well...
— Well then...
— Yes...
Papa, Papa!
What is it, little Kuni?
Look, it's sparkly and pretty...
But it has no value,
it's just a marble, little Kuni.
That's true, Papa...
But...
As long as it's pretty, it doesn't matter
whether it's valueless, right?
kaze ga fuite aa
the wind blows
itai kienai omoi
the pain, the memories won't disappear
nani wo motte ikou ka
what should be brought along?
atsumete hitotsu
assemble them into a piece
nido to nai nido to nai
there is no second chance, never
suteru nante baka mitai
how foolish it is to throw away
mujaki ni natte aa
acting so innocently
imeeji
the images
kitto sore wa owaranai
it probably will not end
ai no mune kogase
burn that love-filled heart
sen no yume watare
sail across a thousand dreams
juuoumujin kakete
running freely
te ni tsukamu sekai
to take hold of the world in hand
kumo ga chigirete
the clouds scatter
hi ga mata ochite
the sun sets yet again
hitori no pareedo ga ugokidasu
the solo parade begins to move
bouken kichijitsu shinpaku joushou
adventure, lucky day, geart beat, rising
meian souguu seimei souai
decisive, encounter, life, mutual love
All right, I'm fired up!
Our mission this time is a treasure hunt!
But your recent low mission
success rate concerns me.
No need to worry.
We've got a map, so it'll be a cinch!
I've thought about it, you see...
No need to think!
If you fail this mission...
It'll be okay, I tell you!
You'll all start over again
from the Academy!
What?!
Next time:
"Dig here, arf-arf. Search for the Buried Treasure."